----------------------------------------------------

Last Updated: 3/8/24

Your privacy is important to us.  This Privacy Policy explains how Built In, Inc. (“Built In,” “we,” or “us”) collects, uses, and discloses information through its website, [www.builtin.com](http://www.builtin.com/) (the “Site”).  The services provided on the Site are referred to as “Services.” We encourage you to become familiar with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By accessing and using the Site, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy and you acknowledge the applicability of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services. 

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Information you provide directly to us.**  When you create an account and otherwise use the Site and Services, you may provide us with certain information such as:

* **PROFILE INFORMATION** THAT YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE, SUCH AS YOUR NAME, EMAIL ADDRESS, AND WORK/EDUCATION HISTORY.
* **AUTHENTICATION INFORMATION,** INCLUDING A USERNAME AND PASSWORD.
* **CORRESPONDENCE** BETWEEN YOU AND US AND RECORDS OF SUCH CORRESPONDENCE, SUCH AS THE CONTENTS OF EMAILS YOU SEND US, SUPPORT INQUIRIES, OR OTHER FEEDBACK YOU PROVIDE DIRECTLY TO US.
* INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE IN **REVIEWS AND SURVEYS;** AND
* **MARKETING PREFERENCES,** SUCH AS RECORDS OF YOUR REQUESTS TO OPT OUT OF MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS.
* **JOB APPLICATION INFORMATION AND RESUMES** INCLUDING WHEN YOU APPLY TO AN EMPLOYER THROUGH OUR ‘EASY APPLY’ FEATURE.
* **PREFERENCES AND INTERESTS** INFORMATION THAT YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE US IN YOUR PROFILE.
* OTHER INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE TO US.  

**Information we obtain from external sources.**  

We and our service providers may use the information you provide to us to search for publicly available information (such as your business expertise, skills, current and past job titles, education, activity on other publicly available websites, and your city location) to create an enhanced profile that is available to employers that have subscribed to our Premium Employer service (“Premium Employers”). If you choose to log in to the Site with a third-party social media site such as Facebook or Google, we may collect information from such third-party social media site, in which case we will ask for your consent prior to your logging in to the Site using your social media account.

When you interact with our social media pages, such as by “liking” our page or posting comments or replies to our content, we may collect certain information about you, consistent with your privacy settings on that platform. If you do not wish for us to collect information from these third parties, please do not interact with us via third-party platforms.

**Information we collect automatically from your device.** 

Like many other websites, Built In and its service providers and partners may also collect certain information pertaining to you and the device and communications method that you use to access our Site and Services. We refer to this information as “Usage Information.” This Usage Information allows us to optimize the Site based on visitors’ device type and analyze and improve the Site and Services. We collect this information automatically as you navigate through and interact with our Site and Services. Usage Information includes: (i) traffic data, general location data inferred from IP address, logs, pages visited, referring URL, length and frequency of your visit to the Site and use of the Services, the resources that you access and use on the Site and Services, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages and content viewed and the order of those pages, the date and time you used the Services, error logs, and other similar information; and (ii) information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, device identifiers, operating system, browser type, browser language, and operating system.

Consistent with your consent preferences and applicable law, we may use the following third-party technologies for this automatic data collection of usage information:

•    Cookies (or browser cookies): A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. We use cookies to keep track of your login information.  You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you use the Site.

•    Pixel Tags / Web Beacons: Pages of our website and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email. We may also use these web beacons for other related Site and email statistics (e.g., recording the popularity of certain content and verifying system and server integrity). For example, you may receive targeted notifications of available job postings based on the content or the pages you click on.

•    Device identifiers:  When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access our Site, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by us.

We use third parties to assist us in serving advertisements, tracking site usage statistics, and providing content-sharing services to support the Services.  These third parties may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and tailor and serve you advertisements across platforms. We do not control these third-party technologies, and their use of your information is governed by those parties' privacy policies. For more information about how to opt out of these third parties’ use of your information, please see the “Personalized content, advertising, and your choices” section below.

Please note that you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., [Microsoft Edge](https://builtin.com/blank), [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en), [Mozilla Firefox](http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox), or [Apple Safari](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042)). As stated above, by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features or offerings of the Services. You may also adjust your cookies preferences by clicking the “Your Privacy Choices/Cookie Settings” link available in the footer of our Site.

**2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We and our service providers may use the information that we collect from or about you to:

* _PROVIDE THE SITE AND SERVICES TO YOU_, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO MAINTAINING YOUR PROFILE PAGE, FACILITATING YOUR SUBMISSION OF AN APPLICATION TO EMPLOYERS PARTICIPATING IN OUR “EASY APPLY” SERVICE, SUPPLEMENTING YOUR PROFILE PAGE WITH PUBLICLY AVAILABLE INFORMATION, AND PROVIDING, OPERATING, ADMINISTERING, AND TROUBLESHOOTING THE SERVICES;
* _COMMUNICATE WITH YOU_, INCLUDING BY INFORMING YOU OF ANY RELEVANT JOB POSTINGS THAT MAY BE OF INTEREST TO YOU BASED UPON YOUR EXPRESSED INTERESTS, RESPONDING TO YOUR INQUIRIES, TO MANAGE YOUR PARTICIPATION IN EVENTS, TO NOTIFY YOU OF CHANGES MADE TO THE SITE, TO CONNECT YOU WITH RECRUITERS FOR VARIOUS JOB OPPORTUNITIES, AND TO SEND YOU PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS THAT YOU REQUEST FROM US;
* _ANALYZE AND IMPROVE THE CONTENT, MATERIALS, AND SERVICES THAT WE MAKE AVAILABLE ON THE SITE_, AND EVALUATE USER NEEDS;
* _CUSTOMIZE THE SERVICES_, INCLUDING BY DISPLAYING INFORMATION RELEVANT TO YOUR EXPRESSED INTERESTS AND PREFERENCES AND GENERATING RECOMMENDATIONS FOR JOBS THAT YOU MAY BE INTERESTED IN 
* _ADVERTISE AND MARKET THE SERVICES,_ INCLUDING BY ALLOWING US AND OUR ADVERTISING PARTNERS TO PERSONALIZE THE CONTENT AND ADVERTISING THAT YOU SEE ON THE SERVICES AND ON THIRD-PARTY PLATFORMS;
* _SECURE THE SITE AND SERVICES AND PROTECT AGAINST FRAUD_ IN ORDER TO PROTECT THE RIGHTS, PROPERTY, OR SAFETY OF BUILT IN, OUR CUSTOMERS, OR OTHERS;
* _COMPLY WITH OUR LEGAL OBLIGATIONS_; AND 
* FOR OTHER _LEGITIMATE AND LAWFUL BUSINESS_ PURPOSES INCLUDING INTERNAL AUDITING AND RECORDKEEPING PURPOSES, AND TO ENFORCE THE LEGAL OR CONTRACTUAL TERMS THAT GOVERN YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE OR DEFEND OUR LEGAL RIGHTS.

If you contact us for support or assistance, we may use information about you or your system that you provide or that we collect for purposes such as verifying whether your system meets the minimum requirements needed to use the Site and our various Services.

We and our Service providers may store your information for as long as needed for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy, which may be indefinitely. We and our Service providers may store your information in the United States, or we may transfer it to other countries.

 **Aggregate and deidentified information.**  We may aggregate and/or deidentify any of the information we collect so that such information no longer identifies you (“Aggregate/deidentified information”). We may use such information for any purposes, including without limitation to gain insight into job trends, job availability and skills needed for jobs; salary trends, and other information related to job seeking, recruiting and branding. We may also share such data with any third parties without limitation.

 **Combined Information**. For the purposes discussed in this Privacy Policy, we may combine the information that we collect through the Services with information that we receive from other sources, both online and offline, and use such combined information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**3\. WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**  

We may disclose your information to parties outside of Built In under the following circumstances:

* **AFFILIATES.** WE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION TO OUR AFFILIATES AND SUBSIDIARIES UNDER COMMON OWNERSHIP AND/OR CONTROL.
* **TO PREMIUM EMPLOYERS**: UNLESS YOU OPT OUT AS DESCRIBED IN “YOUR CHOICES” BELOW, WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU OR THIRD-PARTY SOURCES WITH PREMIUM EMPLOYERS AND THEIR SERVICE PROVIDERS IN CONNECTION WITH OUR JOB SEARCH AND RECRUITING SERVICES. WE MAY ALSO PROVIDE SUCH PREMIUM EMPLOYERS WITH INFORMATION ON USERS OF THE SITE THAT VISIT THEIR COMPANY PAGE, VIEW OR APPLY TO A JOB POSTED BY THE COMPANY, OR VIEW CONTENT FEATURING THE COMPANY. IF YOU BEGIN THE APPLICATION PROCESS BY CLICKING “APPLY” ON A JOB POSTING, PREMIUM EMPLOYERS MAY ALSO HAVE ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE IN SUCH APPLICATIONS, YOUR BUILT IN USER PROFILE INFORMATION, AND YOUR GENERAL GEOLOCATION, EVEN IF YOU HAVE NOT YET SUBMITTED THE APPLICATION.  SUCH PREMIUM EMPLOYERS MAY USE THIS INFORMATION IN FURTHERANCE OF THEIR RECRUITING EFFORTS, INCLUDING BY CONTACTING YOU.
* **SERVICE PROVIDERS**:  WE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION TO SERVICE PROVIDERS WE USE TO SUPPORT OUR BUSINESS. WE MAY DISCLOSE INFORMATION WITH SUCH SERVICE PROVIDERS TO ALLOW THEM TO PERFORM SERVICES ON OUR BEHALF, SUCH AS CUSTOMER SERVICE, DEBUGGING AND ERROR RESOLUTION, ANALYTICS, DATA STORAGE, ANALYSIS AND PROCESSING, LEGAL, AND OTHER SERVICES.
* **OTHER THIRD PARTIES**: EXCEPT AS PROVIDED HEREIN, WE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES THAT ASSIST IN TAILORING AND SERVING ADVERTISEMENTS THAT ARE RELEVANT TO YOU. WE MAY ALSO ALLOW THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING TECHNOLOGIES (E.G., AD NETWORKS AND AD SERVERS) TO USE COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES ON THE SERVICES TO DELIVER RELEVANT AND TARGETED CONTENT AND ADVERTISING TO YOU ON THE SERVICES AND OTHER WEBSITES YOU VISIT AND APPLICATIONS YOU USE, AS EXPLAINED FURTHER IN “PERSONALIZED CONTENT, ADVERTISING, AND YOUR CHOICES” BELOW.
* **BUSINESS TRANSFERS**:  IN THE EVENT THAT BUILT IN IS INVOLVED IN A MERGER, DIVESTITURE, RESTRUCTURING, REORGANIZATION, DISSOLUTION, OR OTHER SALE OR TRANSFER OF SOME OR ALL OF OUR ASSETS, WHETHER AS A GOING CONCERN OR AS PART OF BANKRUPTCY, LIQUIDATION, OR SIMILAR PROCEEDING, YOUR INFORMATION HELD BY US MAY BE AMONG THE ASSETS TRANSFERRED.
* **LEGAL PURPOSES**:  NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING TO THE CONTRARY IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, WE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION IN ORDER TO COMPLY WITH ANY COURT ORDER, LAW, OR LEGAL PROCESS, INCLUDING TO RESPOND TO ANY GOVERNMENT OR REGULATORY REQUEST, OR IF WE BELIEVE DISCLOSURE IS NECESSARY OR APPROPRIATE TO PROTECT THE RIGHTS, PROPERTY, OR SAFETY OF BUILT IN, OUR CUSTOMERS, OR OTHERS. THIS INCLUDES EXCHANGING INFORMATION WITH OTHER COMPANIES AND ORGANIZATIONS FOR THE PURPOSES OF FRAUD PROTECTION AND CREDIT RISK REDUCTION.
* **ENFORCEMENT**: WE MAY ALSO USE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO ESTABLISH OR EXERCISE OUR LEGAL RIGHTS, TO ENFORCE THE TERMS OF USE, TO ASSERT AND DEFEND AGAINST LEGAL CLAIMS, OR IF WE BELIEVE SUCH DISCLOSURE IS NECESSARY TO INVESTIGATE, PREVENT, OR TAKE OTHER ACTION REGARDING ACTUAL OR SUSPECTED ILLEGAL OR FRAUDULENT ACTIVITIES OR POTENTIAL THREATS TO THE PHYSICAL SAFETY OR WELL-BEING OF ANY PERSON.
* DISCLOSED WHEN COLLECTED OR WITH **YOUR CONSENT**:  FOR ANY OTHER PURPOSE DISCLOSED BY US WHEN YOU PROVIDE THE INFORMATION OR OTHERWISE WITH YOUR CONSENT.

**4\. PERSONALIZED CONTENT, ADVERTISING, AND YOUR CHOICES**

Consistent with your consent preferences and applicable law, we may use third-party technologies to engage in analytics and advertising.

**Online Analytics.** We may use third-party web analytics services on our Services, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use the sort of technology previously described in the “Information We Collect” section to help us analyze how users use the Services including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive. The information (including your IP address) collected by the technology will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Services. We also use Google Analytics for certain purposes related to advertising, as described in the following section. To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), or you may opt out of analytics cookies by clicking the “Your Privacy Choices/Cookie Settings” link in the footer of our Site and adjusting your preferences accordingly. 

**Tailored Advertising.** We may personalize the content and advertising that you see when using the Services through the use of third-party advertising technologies that allow for the delivery of relevant content and advertising on the Services, as well as other websites you visit and other applications you use. The ads may be based on various factors such as the content of the page you are visiting, information you provide such as your age and gender, your searches, demographic data, and other information we collect from you. These ads may be based on your current activity or your activity over time and may be tailored to your interests.

Also, third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised via the Services may also place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, mobile phone, or other device to collect information about your use of the Services in order to (i) inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our websites and other sites and (ii) report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our websites and use of our Services. We also may disclose a hashed version of your email address with third-party advertising partners for purposes of delivering tailored advertising. We neither have access to, nor does this Privacy Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed on your computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Services by non-affiliated, third-party ad technology, ad servers, ad networks or any other non-affiliated third parties. Those parties that use these technologies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting as described below.  If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer to deliver tailored advertising, you may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. You may also use the "Your Privacy Choices/Cookie Settings" link in the footer of our Site to control your cookie preferences.

**5\. YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES**

You have certain rights and choices with respect to your information.

**Information you provide to us.** When corresponding with Built In or our representatives, or when making a request for information or otherwise interacting with us or others through the Site, you choose what information to supply, what questions or comments to submit, whether you wish to receive further information, and by what method of communication such information should be delivered. Please take care to disclose only such information as is needed or that you believe is appropriate. While you can browse our site without providing us information, we may not be able to provide you the services you request without collecting certain identifying information.  

**Job Seeker Database.** When you create an account on the Site, you will automatically be listed on Built In’s database of job seekers which can be accessed and searched by Premium Employers and employers. If you do not wish to be listed on this database, you may opt out of being listed on the database by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://builtin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject line “opt out.”

**Delete Your Account**.  You may delete your account by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://builtin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  Please be advised that, even if we successfully delete your account, employers who have accessed your profile may have retained a copy of your Information for their own files. We cannot control the retention or use of your information once they have been downloaded by third parties, and you will not be able to delete information held by those third parties.

**Marketing Communications.** You can unsubscribe from marketing emails we send to you by clicking the “unsubscribe” link they contain. Please note that even though you may opt-out of receiving marketing-related communications from us, we may still send you important administrative and transactional messages.

**Rights Regarding Your Information.** Depending on your jurisdiction, you may have the right, in accordance with applicable data protection laws, to make requests related to your “personal information” or “personal data” (as such terms are defined under applicable law, and collectively referred to herein as “personal information”). Specifically, you may have the right to ask us to: 

* INFORM YOU ABOUT THE CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT OR DISCLOSE ABOUT YOU; THE CATEGORIES OF SOURCES OF SUCH INFORMATION; THE BUSINESS OR COMMERCIAL PURPOSE FOR COLLECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION; AND THE CATEGORIES OF THIRD PARTIES WITH WHOM WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION.
* PROVIDE YOU ACCESS TO AND/OR A COPY OF CERTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION WE HOLD ABOUT YOU.
* CORRECT OR UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE HOLD ABOUT YOU.
* DELETE CERTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION WE HAVE ABOUT YOU.
* PROVIDE YOU WITH INFORMATION ABOUT THE FINANCIAL INCENTIVES THAT WE OFFER TO YOU, IF ANY.
* RESTRICT OR OBJECT TO CERTAIN USES OF YOUR INFORMATION.
* WITHDRAW YOUR CONSENT TO PROCESSING OF YOUR INFORMATION, WHERE YOU HAVE PROVIDED YOUR AFFIRMATIVE CONSENT TO PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION FOR A SPECIFIC PURPOSE.
* OPT YOU OUT OF THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR PURPOSES OF PROFILING IN FURTHERANCE OF DECISIONS THAT PRODUCE LEGAL OR SIMILARLY SIGNIFICANT EFFECTS, IF APPLICABLE. 

Please note that certain information may be exempt from such requests under applicable law.  For example, we need certain information in order to provide the Services to you.  

Residents of certain U.S. states may also have the right to opt out of “sales” of your information and “sharing/processing of your information for targeted advertising” as described below. If you are a California resident, please see the “California Privacy Notice” section below for more information about our privacy practices and your rights.

As provided in applicable law, you also have the right to not be discriminated against for exercising your rights. 

We also need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to a request, which may include, at a minimum, depending on the sensitivity of the information you are requesting and the type of request you are making, verifying your name and email address.  If we are unable to verify you, we may be unable to respond to your requests. 

To exercise any of these rights, you can fill out the webform [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/c0c4a969-b926-40b8-ab2b-b691a7a49d38/d590d9e0-4c32-4ee0-8d69-d370f6987d74).

You may be able to designate an authorized agent to make requests on your behalf. In order for an authorized agent to be verified, you must provide the authorized agent with signed, written permission to make such requests or a power of attorney. We may also follow up with you to verify your identity before processing the authorized agent’s request.  

Depending on applicable law, you may have the right to appeal our decision to deny your request, if applicable. We will provide information about how to exercise that right in our response denying the request. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

**Notice of Right to Opt Out of Sales of Personal Information and Processing/Sharing of Personal Information for Targeted Advertising Purposes.** We also permit users to opt out of “sales” of your information and “sharing/processing of your information for targeted advertising,” as those terms are defined under US state privacy laws.

As explained in the “When we disclose your information” section above, we sometimes disclose information to unaffiliated third parties we collaborate with or that provide offers that we think may be of value to you. We also provide information to third-party advertising providers for targeted advertising purposes or use advertising analytics partners to assist us in analyzing use of our services and our user/customer base. Under applicable law, the disclosure of your personal information to these third parties to assist us in providing these services may be considered a “sale” of personal information or the processing/sharing of personal information for targeted advertising purposes.

If you would like to opt out of the disclosure of your personal information for purposes that could be considered “sales” for those third parties' own commercial purposes, or “sharing” or processing for purposes of targeted advertising, please visit the " Your Privacy Choices/Cookie Settings " link in the footer of our Site. Note that you will need to opt out on each browser you use to access the Services.

Depending on your jurisdiction, you may be permitted to designate an authorized agent to submit such requests on your behalf. Please note that we do not knowingly sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**Inquiries and Complaints.** If you have any concerns or complaints about how we process your information, we urge you to first try to resolve such issues directly with us by contacting us via the information provided in the “Contact Us” section below. However, you may have the right under applicable law to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority in your country, or seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been violated.

**6\. INTERNATIONAL VISITORS**

**Data Transfers.** Built In is headquartered in the United States, but we may feature jobs located in other countries, and users in other countries may register for our platform and apply to jobs featured on our platform. Accordingly, we may transfer, store, and/or process your information with third parties, such as Premium Employers and our trusted service providers, in locations around the world (including the United States) for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Wherever your information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we protect your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. These measures may include implementing Standard Contractual Clauses to govern the transfer of your information, or other means recognized by applicable laws. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge any such transfer, storage, or processing.

**Legal Bases for Processing.** The laws in some jurisdictions require us to tell you about the legal grounds we rely on to process your information. Our legal bases for processing your information as described in this Privacy Policy are as follows:

* Performance of our obligations under a contract or commitment to you. For example, we process your personal information to comply with our website terms of service.
* In furtherance of our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others (including our Premium Employers). For example, we process information to secure our services, to help us and our Premium Employers analyze how job seekers use our platform, defend our legal rights, and prevent fraud.
* Compliance with applicable legal obligations. For example, we retain information for as long as needed to comply with applicable laws.
* With your affirmative consent. Where required by law, we process your information on the basis of your consent to processing for a particular purpose, such as to send you marketing communications.

**7\. PROTECTION OF INFORMATION**

Built In and our service providers take measures to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal data by aiming to maintain appropriate physical, procedural and electronic safeguards to protect your personal data, including:

•    Restricting access to personal data to our employees and Service providers on a “need to know” basis;

•    Enforcing policies and procedures for our employees in their handling of personal data; and

•    Using technologies designed to safeguard data during its transmission, such as SSL encryption for the data you provide on our websites.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk and we do not guarantee that information that you transmit or otherwise supply to us, or any communications conducted on or through the Site, is or will be totally secure. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. If you become aware of any breach of Site security, this Privacy Policy, or the Terms of Use, please notify us immediately.

**8\. CHILDREN UNDER AGE 16**

Our Site is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may register for the Services or send us personal information. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on the Site or Services. If we learn we have collected or received the personal information of a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://builtin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**9\. CHANGES TO THE POLICY**

From time to time, we may change our privacy practices, and this Privacy Policy, because of changes in relevant and applicable legal or regulatory requirements, in our business or our business practices, or in our attempts to better serve your needs and those of our other members. We will make the revised Privacy Policy available on this page, so you should review the Policy periodically. The date of the most recent revision to the policy is identified herein. If we make a material change to the Policy, we will provide you with appropriate notice in accordance with legal requirements. By continuing to access and use the Site, you are confirming that you have read and understood the latest version of this Policy.

**10\. THIRD PARTY LINKS**

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected at this Site. It does not apply to any other websites.  For instance, if you click “Apply Now” on a job posting on the Site, we may redirect you to such employer’s career site to submit a resume or application.  Information collected through such third party sites is not subject to this Privacy Policy, but instead is subject to such third party service provider’s privacy policy.  We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of each website that you visit.

**11\.** **RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We generally retain personal data for so long as it may be relevant to the purposes above.  In determining how long to retain information, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the information, the purposes for which we process the information, applicable legal requirements, and our legitimate interests. The purposes for which we process information (as well as the other factors listed above) may dictate different retention periods for the same types of information. If you opt out of email marketing, we maintain your email on our suppression list for an extended time to comply with your request. To dispose of your information, we may anonymize it, delete it or take other appropriate steps.  Data may persist in copies made for backup and business continuity purposes for additional time.  

**12\. ANY QUESTIONS? PLEASE CONTACT US AT:**

Built In, Inc.

222 W Merchandise Mart Plaza, Ste. 2010, Chicago, IL 60654

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://builtin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**13\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE**

 If you are a California resident, California law requires us to provide you with some additional information regarding your rights with respect to the “personal information” (as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)) we collect from and about you, and your rights with respect to your personal information.

We describe the categories of information we collect, our business purposes for collecting such information, the sources and uses of such information and the entities with which we disclose such information in the “Information we collect”, “How we use your information,” and “When we disclose your information” sections of this Privacy Policy.  We provide additional information required by the CCPA below.

**A.    Categories of Personal Information we collect, use and disclose**

This following section provides information about the categories of personal information that we collect, the purposes for which we use the information, the sources of the information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose the information for business purposes. The following are the “categories” of personal information under the CCPA that we collect from California consumers and that we may use and disclose for our business purposes, as discussed throughout this Privacy Policy.

**Category of information collected**

* **NAME AND CONTACT INFORMATION:** SUCH AS YOUR NAME AND E-MAIL ADDRESS
* **LOGIN CREDENTIALS**
* **CUSTOMER SERVICE INFORMATION:** SUCH AS QUESTIONS AND OTHER MESSAGES YOU ADDRESS TO US THROUGH ONLINE FORMS, BY E-MAIL, OVER THE PHONE, OR BY POST; AND SUMMARIES OR VOICE RECORDINGS OF YOUR INTERACTIONS WITH CUSTOMER CARE.
* **EMPLOYMENT OR EDUCATION INFORMATION:** SUCH AS EDUCATION HISTORY AND RESUME
* **JOB APPLICATION INFORMATION AND RESUMES** IF YOU ARE APPLYING TO AN EMPLOYER VIA BUILT IN’S ‘EASY APPLY’ FEATURE.
* **OTHER JOB SEEKER PROFILE INFORMATION:** SUCH AS YOUR GENDER, PHOTOGRAPH, AND WORK PREFERENCES AND INTERESTS
* **SOCIAL MEDIA INFORMATION:** IF YOU LINK YOUR ACCOUNT OR ACCESS THE SERVICES THROUGH A THIRD-PARTY CONNECTION OR LOG-IN, WE MAY HAVE ACCESS TO ANY INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO THAT SOCIAL NETWORK DEPENDING ON YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS SUCH AS YOUR NAME, E-MAIL ADDRESS, FRIEND LIST, PHOTO, GENDER, LOCATION, AND CURRENT CITY; AND INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US DIRECTLY THROUGH OUR PAGES ON SOCIAL NETWORKING AND BLOGGING PLATFORMS (E.G., FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM, AND TWITTER)
* **DEVICE INFORMATION AND IDENTIFIERS SUCH AS IP ADDRESS**; BROWSER TYPE AND LANGUAGE; OPERATING SYSTEM; PLATFORM TYPE; DEVICE TYPE; SOFTWARE AND HARDWARE ATTRIBUTES; AND UNIQUE DEVICE IDENTIFIERS
* **USAGE DATA:** SUCH AS TRAFFIC DATA, LOGS, PAGES VISITED, REFERRING URL, LENGTH AND FREQUENCY OF YOUR VISIT TO THE SITE, AND THE RESOURCES THAT YOU ACCESS AND USE ON THE SITE
* **GENERAL GEOLOCATION INFORMATION:** SUCH AS CITY, STATE AND ZIP CODE ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR IP ADDRESS, OR NAME OF CITY AND STATE THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US OR ON OTHER SITES

**How we use these categories of personal information**

We and our service providers may use the categories of personal information we collect from and about you for the following business and commercial purposes (as those terms are defined in applicable law).  

* PROVIDE THE SITE AND SERVICES (E.G., ACCOUNT SERVICING AND MAINTENANCE, CUSTOMER SERVICE, ADVERTISING AND MARKETING, ANALYTICS, AND COMMUNICATION ABOUT THE SERVICES);
* ANALYZE AND IMPROVE THE CONTENT, MATERIALS AND SERVICES AVAILABLE ON THE SITE;
* ASSIST YOU IN APPLYING TO JOBS;
* COMMUNICATE WITH YOU;
* CUSTOMIZING CONTENT THAT WE OR OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS DISPLAY ON THE SERVICES (E.G., CONTEXTUAL ADS);
* SECURE THE SITE AND SERVICES AND PROTECT AGAINST FRAUD INCLUDING BUG DETECTION AND ERROR REPORTING;
* DETECTING, PROTECTING AGAINST, AND PROSECUTING SECURITY INCIDENTS AND FRAUDULENT OR ILLEGAL ACTIVITY;
* OTHER USES THAT ADVANCE OUR COMMERCIAL OR ECONOMIC INTERESTS, SUCH AS THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING AND COMMUNICATING WITH YOU ABOUT RELEVANT OFFERS FROM THIRD PARTY PARTNERS; AND
* OTHER USES ABOUT WHICH WE NOTIFY YOU.

Further explanation of these types of uses are discussed in our Privacy Policy in the “How we use your information” section.  We may also use the categories of personal information for compliance with applicable laws and regulations, and we may combine the information we collect (“aggregate”) or remove pieces of information (“de-identify”) to limit or prevent identification of any user or device. We may also disclose this information to third parties for legal, compliance or security purposes, or in connection with a business transfer, as described further in “When we disclose your information” above.

**B. Sale/Sharing of Personal Information** 

The CCPA sets forth certain obligations for businesses that “sell” personal information or “share” personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes. Under the CCPA, “sale” and “sharing” are defined such that they may include allowing third parties to receive certain information for advertising purposes.  We “sell” or “share” the following categories of information to third-party advertising partners and vendors that support our advertising efforts (such as advertising analytics services): 

**Device information and identifiers such as IP address**; **Usage Data; General geolocation information**

If you would like to opt out of our use of your information for such purposes that are considered a “sale” or “sharing” for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes under California law, please visit the " Your Privacy Choices/Cookie Settings " link in the footer of our Site. Alternatively, if you have a legally-recognized browser-based opt out preference signal turned on via your device browser, we recognize such preference in accordance with applicable law. Please note that we do not knowingly sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**C. Additional California Rights**

If you are a California resident, the CCPA allows you to make certain requests about your personal information. Please see the “Your Rights and Your Choices” section of our Policy above for information about the rights you have with respect to your personal information under California law and how to exercise them. 

If we ever offer any financial incentives in exchange for your personal information, we will provide you with appropriate information about such incentives. 

The CCPA also allows you to limit the use or disclosure of your “sensitive personal information” (as defined in the CCPA) if your sensitive personal information is used for certain purposes. Please note, in the limited circumstances that we process sensitive personal information (such as usernames in combination with passwords) as defined in the CCPA, we do not use or disclose it other than for disclosed and permitted business purposes for which there is not a right to limit under the CCPA. We ask that users not include sensitive information in application materials, such as your resume. 

**D. Shine the Light**

California Law permits customers who are California residents to request certain information once per year regarding our disclosure of “personal information” (as that term is defined under applicable California law) to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

**Any questions? Please contact us at:**

Built In, Inc.

203 N LaSalle St Suite 2200

Chicago, Illinois 60601

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://builtin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Built In is the online community for startups and tech companies. Find startup jobs, tech news and events.

About

Get Involved

Resources

Tech Hubs

© Built In 2024
